katyperrycollections.com 2017-11-20

# privacy

## Privacy Policy

Last updated: February 1, 2017

This Privacy Policy applies to information that each of Purrfect Ventures as a division of GBG USA Inc., and their parent, subsidiary and affiliate entities worldwide (individually referred to herein as the “the Company” or “we” or “us” or “our”) collects about you on or through [KatyPerryCollections.com](http://www.katyperrycollections.com/), or one of our other websites, applications or other services from which you are accessing this Privacy Policy (each referred to herein as a “Site” and collectively, the “Sites”). This Privacy Policy describes how we collect such information, how we use it and to whom and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Personal Information includes, but is not limited to, your name, postal address, zip or postal code, email address, telephone number, date of birth, payment information, demographic information, details on items purchased, and other information you choose to provide us (“Personal Information”). The Personal Information we collect is stored and/or controlled by Purrfect Ventures LLC in New York, NY and/or the relevant local corporate affiliate(s).

We may share and use your Personal Information with our parent, subsidiary and affiliate entities for marketing purposes and use in connection with their websites and their services. We may share your Personal Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes as further described in our Information Disclosure and Your Choices/Your Privacy Rights sections below.

### California Privacy Rights

Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code provides that residents of California can obtain certain information about their personal information (as defined under Section 1798.83(e)(6) of the California Civil Code) that companies have shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year, as well as the identity of those third parties. Personal information, as defined under the California Civil Code, includes, but is not limited to, data relating to a living individual who is or can be identified either from the data or from the data in conjunction with other information that is in, or is likely to come into, the possession of the data controller. To request a copy of your personal information maintained by us, please contact us at [info@KatyPerryCollections.com](mailto:info@katyperrycollections.com).

## Information Collection

### Information You Provide To Us

We (or our service providers) collect information from you when you: (1) purchase products from us on our Sites; (2) create an account with us (the “Account”), or otherwise sign up for a service or feature; (3) complete a survey; (4) participate in a sweepstakes, contest or other promotion; (5) communicate with us via third-party social media sites; (6) apply for a job with us; or (7) contact us, or otherwise communicate with us or provide information to us.

In some cases, you may provide information to us about another person, such as when you purchase a gift card for someone and request that we deliver it to that person, when you share Site content or send a message to a friend through a Site or otherwise, or when you decide to ship products you purchase to someone else. In such cases, you represent that you have the authorization of such person to provide us with such information.

We may combine your (and others’) information that we’ve collected from you (or others) with information we may receive from other sources, such as third-party social media platforms (e.g., when you choose to log in to our Sites through a third-party social media platform, subject to your actions and settings thereon), address update services and co-promotion partners. By accessing our Sites, you signify your consent to the above collection of your Personal Information.

When you are creating an Account for the first time on a Site with an email address that you have previously provided to us in another circumstance (e.g., when signing up for our emails, by entering one of our sweepstakes or other promotions), we may recognize that email address and, once you have completed the account set-up process, you may be able to see your contact information already included in your new online Account. This is happening because we have recognized your email address and, for your convenience, have added your information to your Account. If you do not want us to collect your Personal Information, please do not provide it to us. You can update your Personal Information or change marketing and subscription settings by accessing your Account via the Sites.

### Site Information & Other Information Collected Automatically

As part of the standard operation of the Sites, certain Personal Information is collected automatically or passively from or about you in connection with your visit to the Sites. Our servers may automatically gather some of the Site Usage Information (as defined below), or we (or our service providers) may use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect and track such information.

Site Usage Information includes, but is not limited to: (i) your browser type, device type, carrier (if applicable), device address, operating system, operating system address, IP address and the domain name from which you accessed a Site; (ii) information about your region, continent, country, city, zip code, time zone, and general location; and (iii) information about your browsing activities on and through a Site (also known as “Click Stream” data), such as (a) the date and time you visit one of the Sites, (b) the areas or pages of a Site that you visit, (c) the amount of time you spend viewing a Site or specific areas of a Site, (d) the number of times you return to a Site or a specific area of a Site, (e) the web sites or pages you visited prior to visiting a Site, (f) the websites or pages you visit after you leave a Site; (g) searches you have performed on a Site and on other websites that led you to our Sites; (h) social plug-ins with which you have interacted on our Sites; and (j) other similar Site usage data (collectively, the “Site Usage Information”).

We consider this Site Usage Information, on its own, to be non-personal in nature, unless required otherwise by applicable law. However, we may combine Site Usage Information about you with Personal Information about you, and we would consider the combined information to be “personally identifiable” or Personal Information for the purposes of this Privacy Policy.

### Browser Do-Not Track Signals

Some web browsers and devices permit you to broadcast a preference that you not be “tracked” online. At this time, we do not modify your experience based on whether such a signal is broadcast. To learn more about browser tracking signals and “Do Not Track,” please visit http://allaboutdnt.com.

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We and our service providers may use cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, Adobe Flash Technology and other similar technologies, which allow us to, among other things, optimize our Sites and to understand traffic and usage patterns. Additionally, if the settings on your location-aware device allow us to receive geo-location data or information, we may collect that information automatically.

A cookie is a small data file that is sent to your web browser and placed on your computer or device when you access a website. Cookies allow parties (including us, our service providers and others) to: (i) track your activities on the Sites, (ii) track clicks, purchases and conversion; (iii) recognize your computer or device so that you are able to save your preference and stay logged in to the Sites without having to re-enter your Account credentials; (iv) deliver customized content, messages and advertising to you; (v) preserve the contents of your shopping cart; (vi) and otherwise enhance and personalize your experience on the Sites. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, most devices allow you to decline the use of cookies. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because if you elect not to allow them, you may not be able to use or to enjoy all of the services and features of the Sites.

We may use Flash cookies and other similar technologies, which allow a website to store certain information locally on an individual’s computer or device and then access and use that information to enhance and facilitate certain Site experiences, processes and functionality. Flash cookies are different from other cookies and may not be removed in the same manner. More information about both kinds of cookies is available at www.allaboutcookies.org.

We also use web beacons (also known as “clear GIFs” or “pixel tags”) for similar purposes as cookies. These beacons are typically one-pixel images that are embedded in the Site or in a communication, such as an email message. These technologies help us to verify when a certain page of a Site is viewed, when a message is opened and when links or other content in a message are clicked or viewed. We may use third party web analytics services, such as Google Analytics and Adobe services, to help us track and analyze the use of our Site and to measure the effectiveness of our advertising, Site content, and communications. These service providers’ tools, including, for example, cookies, tags and web beacons, help us to gain this understanding.

### Advertising on the Site and Other Websites

We also work with service providers and partner with advertising companies that use cookies, web beacons and other tools to collect information about your visits to and behavior on the Sites and other websites, and then use that information to deliver targeted advertisements to you across the Internet. The information collected and used in this manner is generally, on its own, anonymous and not personally identifiable.

### Information Use

We may use the information we collect from and about you (including both Personal Information and Site Usage Information) for a variety of purposes, including but not limited to the following:

(i) To fulfill your requests for products and services and to keep you informed about your orders; (ii) to provide you with targeted offers and advertising on and at the Sites; (iii) subject to your communications preferences and, where required by applicable law, subject to your consent, to contact you (via postal mail, email and the like) with promotional materials about us, our products, our services and our events, as well as about select partners; (iv) to contact you when necessary or appropriate; where appropriate, for market research and to review and improve our merchandise selections, customer service, online and offline operations and overall shopping experience; (v) to protect the security or integrity of the Sites and our business; (vi) and otherwise, with your permission or as permitted by law.

If you provide us with information about another person (as described above in the “Information You Provide To Us” section), where permitted applicable by law, we use that information to fulfill your requests and treat such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We (and our service providers) also analyze and use Site Usage Information and information collected through cookies, web beacons and other tracking technologies, alone and in combination with Personal Information, to assess the behavior of our users, to measure the interest in and use of the Sites and communications, and to customize the Sites and our communications with you. We do this both on an individual basis and in the aggregate.

### Information Disclosure

We may disclose information we collect (including Site Usage Information and Personal Information) in the following ways, to the extent permitted by law:

  * To our service providers and suppliers, who collect or use such information for us or on our behalf (such as website or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, email service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, and other similar entities that help us to operate the Site and/or provide functionality, content and services);

  * As necessary, if we believe that there has been a violation of the Sites’ Terms of Use or any other policy of the Sites, or if we have reason to believe that our rights or property, or the rights or property of any third party, may be or have been harmed;

  * To respond to subpoenas or other judicial processes, or to provide information as requested by law;

  * In the event that Purrfect Ventures LLC or substantially all of its assets are acquired by one or more third parties as a result of an acquisition, merger, sale, consolidation, bankruptcy, liquidation or other similar corporate reorganization, where your information may be one of the transferred assets;

  * To third party marketers, as permitted by law;

  * When you contribute to a social, community or other publicly available area or feature of the Sites, the information and content that you post may be made available to the general public, depending on your settings (which is why we recommend that you do not submit or post any sensitive Personal Information, such as your full name, home address, phone number or other information that would enable others to contact or locate you); and

  * As otherwise, with your permission or as permitted by law. Content and information that you submit on or through Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Tumblr and other third-party platforms may appear on the Site through feeds from and other interfaces with those platforms. We are not responsible for the information, content and/or privacy practices of any such third-party platforms.

### Your Choices/Your Privacy Rights

If you would like to opt out of receiving direct mail from us, please contact us at [info@KatyPerryCollections.com](mailto:info@katyperrycollections.com). Please understand that if you opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your Account, relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us.

If you would like to opt out of receiving promotional emails from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions located in each such email or contact us at [info@KatyPerryCollections.com](mailto:info@katyperrycollections.com). Please understand that if you opt out of receiving promotional correspondence from us, we may still contact you in connection with your Account, relationship, activities, transactions and communications with us.

If you would prefer that we not share your Personal Information with third-party marketers, please contact us at [info@KatyPerryCollections.com](mailto:info@katyperrycollections.com). Please understand that if you do request that we stop sharing your Personal Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes, such request will only apply as of the date of your request, and we will not be responsible for any communications that you may receive from third parties that received your Personal Information prior to that request. In these cases, please opt out from or contact the third party directly.

### Maintenance and Processing of Information in the U.S. and Other Countries

Your Personal Information and other information may be stored, transferred and processed in and to the United States. By providing Personal Information to us, you consent to the collection, maintenance, processing and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other countries and territories, pursuant to the laws of the United States or such other jurisdictions, which may provide lesser privacy protection than the laws of other countries, and you acknowledge that your Personal Information may thus be subject to U.S. laws and accessible to the U.S. government, courts, law enforcement and regulatory agencies.

### Access to Your Personal Information

You may access any Personal Information you provide to us, correct or modify any such Personal Information, or direct us to delete or make no further use of your Personal Information. You can access or make certain adjustments to your Account directly through your online Account.

## Security

We have implemented measures in an effort to safeguard the Personal Information in our custody and control. Such measures include, for example, limiting access to Personal Information only to employees and authorized service providers who need to know such Personal Information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, as well as other administrative, technical and physical safeguards. Additionally, our service providers are not authorized to use or disclose your Personal Information for any purpose other than providing the services to us or on our behalf, or as otherwise may be required by applicable law. While we endeavor to always protect our systems, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle and other risk factors, we cannot guarantee that any Personal Information, during transmission or while stored on our systems, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers.

To provide you with increased security, access to certain Personal Information stored in your Account is protected with your username and password. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your Account credentials, and we strongly recommend that you do not disclose your Account username or password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in any unsolicited communication. Please notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your Account credentials or any other suspected breach of security.

### Children’s Privacy

The Sites are not directed to children under the age of thirteen (13). If you are under the age of thirteen (13), do not provide your Personal Information on or to the Site. We do not knowingly collect on the Sites any Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen (13). Users outside of the United States who are below the age of eighteen (18) (or the age of the majority in the applicable jurisdiction) should not use the Sites without authorization from a parent or legal guardian.

### Third-Party Websites

The Sites may contain links (which may take the form of hyperlinks, widgets, clickable logos, plug-ins, images or banners) to websites and services operated by entities other than us. This Privacy Policy does not apply to such websites or services, so we recommend that you review their posted privacy policies so that you understand the relevant information collection, use and disclosure practices.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and the amended policy will be posted to the Sites. We reserve the right to update, change, amend or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the “Last Updated” date at the top of the Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the Sites after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy become effective shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised and then-current Privacy Policy.

### Dispute Resolution/Arbitration

By using the Sites, you agree that any dispute in any manner arising out of or relating in any way to the Privacy Policy, shall be submitted to binding arbitration with Judicial Arbitration and Mediation Services, Inc. (“JAMS”) pursuant to JAMS’ arbitration rules, held before a single neutral arbitrator in the New York, NY area. The parties to arbitration may use legal counsel at their own expense, and the prevailing party shall be entitled to its reasonable attorney’s fees. All costs of arbitration (including arbitrator fees) shall be paid by the Company, except only that if you bring the arbitration, you may be charged an initial filing fee that shall not exceed the filing fees that you would incur for bringing an action in court. This provision will not affect any claimant’s rights to seek relief from small claims court. Claims brought on behalf of or allegedly representing or including other persons or entities, including but not limited to any class, consolidated, representative, collective or private attorney general action, shall be a “Class Action.” Notwithstanding anything else in the Privacy Policy or the JAMS rules, any parties subject to this arbitration provision shall be barred from bringing or participating in any Class Action related to a dispute covered by this arbitration provision. However, if these Class Action restrictions are ever deemed illegal or unenforceable, they shall be severed from this arbitration provision. In that event, any Class Action shall by exempt from this arbitration provision and brought in court. This arbitration provision is subject to the Federal Arbitration Act, and may be enforced in any court of competent jurisdiction.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at [info@KatyPerryCollections.com](mailto:info@katyperrycollections.com).
